fattail.com 2015-12-21

# FatTail: We make it easy for online publishers to price, plan, and sell premium guaranteed inventory. We get you from Quote to Cash Quicker!

Revised: February 24, 2012

Your privacy is very important to us. We have prepared this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use protect, and share information and data when you use the FatTail Web site ("Site") or FatTail services ("Services"). This Privacy Policy also explains your choices for managing your information preferences, including opting out of certain uses of your Personal Information. By using the Site or Services you consent to this Privacy Policy.

Managing Your Information Preferences

You can always review, correct, update, or delete your Personal Information.

You can opt out of receiving certain e-mails from us by e-mailing us at privacy@fattail.com.

E-mail publications from our advertiser and e-mail newsletter publisher clients are sent only to people who have consented to receive that particular e-mail publication or mailing from the client. If at any time you would like to end a subscription to an e-mail publication or mailing, you can follow either the directions posted at the end of the e-mail publication or mailing, or, where applicable, the directions at the particular client's Web site.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at privacy@fattail.com.

Information We Collect

_Personal Information_

In the course of advertisement delivery, FatTail does not collect any Personal Information. We only collect information that personally identifies you, such as your name, address, e-mail, and other personally identifiable information that you choose to provide us with or that one of our clients has provided us with in order to use our Services ("Personal Information"). For e-mail publications from our clients, e-mail addresses may be joined with the information provided at our client's Web site and may be augmented with other data sources. However, FatTail does not link e-mail addresses to any other Web browsing activities or clickstream data.

_Usage Data_

We collect anonymous data about users of our Site and Services ("Usage Data"). For example, each time you use the Site we automatically collect the type of Web browser you use, your operating system, your Internet Service Provider, your IP address, the pages you view, and the time and duration of your visits to the Site. We also collect data regarding whether you responded to an ad delivered. This anonymous information, however, does not identify any specific person. We use Usage Data to improve the quality of our Site and Services and to measure ad effectiveness on behalf of FatTail's advertiser and e-mail newsletter publisher clients who specifically request it.

_Cookies and Web Beacons_

We use cookies (a small text file placed on your computer to identify your computer and browser). We also use Web beacons (an electronic file placed on a Web site that monitors usage). We use cookies and Web beacons to improve the experience of the Site and Services. We do not use cookies or Web beacons to collect Personal Information. Most Web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your Web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, certain features of the Site or Services may not work if you delete or disable cookies. Some of our Service Providers may use their own cookies and Web beacons in connection with the services they perform on our behalf.

How We Use Information and When We May Share Information

_General_

We use Personal Information for internal purposes only, such as providing you with the Site and Services, to improve the Site and Services, to notify you of new products or Services, and to otherwise communicate with you about FatTail, the Site, and the Services. We will not disclose Personal Information to third parties without your consent, except as explained in this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose to third parties, certain Usage Data regarding the Site and Services. However, in such cases, your Usage Data is aggregated with Usage Data of others and does not identify you individually.

_Service Providers_

From time to time, we may establish a business relationship with other businesses whom we believe trustworthy and who have confirmed that their privacy practices are consistent with ours ("Service Providers"). For example, we may contract with Service Providers to provide certain services, such as hosting and maintenance, data storage and management, and marketing and promotions. We only provide our Service Providers with the information necessary for them to perform these services on our behalf. Each Service Provider must agree to use reasonable security procedures and practices, appropriate to the nature of the information involved, in order to protect Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Service Providers are prohibited from using Personal Information other than as specified by FatTail.

_Other Transfers_

We may share Personal Information and Usage Data with businesses controlling, controlled by, or under common control with FatTail. If FatTail is merged, acquired, or sold, or in the event of a transfer of some or all of our assets, we may disclose or transfer Personal Information and Usage Data in connection with such transaction. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if, in our discretion, the new entity plans to handle your information in a way that differs materially from this Privacy Policy.

_Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement_

FatTail cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose Personal Information and any other information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties if, in our discretion, we believe it is necessary or appropriate in order to respond to legal requests (including court orders and subpoenas), to protect the safety, property or rights of FatTail or of any third party, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.

Security

FatTail recognizes the importance of safeguarding the confidentiality of your Personal Information. Accordingly, we maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of information transmitted to us. However, no data transmission over the Internet or other network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect information transmitted on or through the Site or Services, we cannot and do not guarantee the security of any information you transmit on or through the Site or Services, and you do so at your own risk.

Links To Other Web Sites

Our Site and Services may contain links to other Web sites, or allow others to send you such links. A link to a third party's Web site does not mean that we endorse it or that we are affiliated with it. We do not exercise control over third-party Web sites. You access such third-party Web sites or content at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a third-party Web site before providing any information to the Web site.

Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records.

European Union Residents

For European Union and Swiss Residents, if you choose to provide us with your Personal Information, you consent to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers located in the United States.

FatTail adheres to the US-EU Safe Harbor and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity, Access and Enforcement, and is registered with the _U.S. Department of Commerce's Safe Harbor Program_ <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor>

Any questions or concerns regarding the use or disclosure of your information should be directed to FatTail by e-mailing us at privacy@fattail.com. We will investigate and attempt to resolve complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. European Union and Swiss Residents, if your complaints cannot be resolved, we have agreed to participate in the dispute resolution procedures of the American Arbitration Association pursuant to the US-EU Safe Harbor and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Privacy Principles.

Privacy Policy Changes

From time to time, we may change this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will inform you by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Site. Those changes will go into effect on the Revision Date shown in the revised Privacy Policy. Your continued use of our Site or Services constitutes your consent to the revised Privacy Policy.
